const quizDB = [
    {
        question: "Q1: What does HTML stands for?",
        a:"Hypertext machine language",
        b:"Hightext marking language",
        c:"Hypertext markup language",
        d:"Hypertable making language",
        ans:"3"
    },
        
        {
        question: "Q2: Which of the following element used to making any text bold?",
        a:"<p>",
        b:"<i>",
        c:"<li>",
        d:"<b>",
        ans:"4"
        },
        
        {
        question: "Q3: how many heading tags are there in HTML?",
        a:"4",
        b:"6",
        c:"2",
        d:"None of the above",
        ans:"2"
        },
        
        {
        question: "Q4: How is document type initialized in HTML5.?",
        a:"</DOCTYPE HTML>",
        b:"</DOCTYPE>",
        c:"<!DOCTYPE HTML>",
        d:"</DOCTYPE html>",
        ans:"3"
        },
        
        {
        question: "Q5: Which of the following HTML element is used for creating an unordered list?",
        a:"<ul>",
        b:"<i>",
        c:"<li>",
        d:"<ol>",
        ans:"1"
        },
        {
            question: "Q6: Which of the following characters indicate closing of a tag?",
            a:".",
            b:"/",
            c:"//",
            d:"\\",
            ans:"2"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q7: Which of the following attributes is used to open an hyperlink in new tab?",
            a:"tab",
            b:"href",
            c:"target",
            d:"next",
            ans:"3"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q8: How many different styling techniques are used in CSS?",
            a:"2",
            b:"3",
            c:"4",
            d:"1",
            ans:"2"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q9: Using padding clears the area outside:",
            a:"Border",
            b:"Content",
            c:"Margin",
            d:"All of the above",
            ans:"2"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q10: Which HTML tag is used for internal style sheet?",
            a:"Internal",
            b:"Internal Style",
            c:"link",
            d:"Style",
            ans:"4"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q11: Which of the following property is used to align the text of a document?",
            a:" text-indent",
            b:"text-align",
            c:" text-decoration",
            d:" text-transform",
            ans:"2"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q12: Which of the following property is used to set the text shadow around a text?",
            a:"white-space",
            b:"text-shadow",
            c:"text-decoration",
            d:"text-transform",
            ans:"2"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q13: Which of the following property of a anchor element signifies an element on which the user is currently clicking?",
            a:"link",
            b:"viseted",
            c:"hover",
            d:"active",
            ans:"4"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q14: Which of the following property specifies the left padding of an element?",
            a:" padding-left",
            b:" padding-right",
            c:" padding-top",
            d:" padding-bottom",
            ans:"1"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q15: What does CSS stands for?",
            a:" Cascading super sheet",
            b:" Cascading style sheet",
            c:" casting super sheet",
            d:" casting style sheet",
            ans:"2"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q16:Javascript is a _____ language.",
            a:" Programming",
            b:" Application",
            c:" Scripting",
            d:" None of the above",
            ans:"3"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q17:JavaScript can be written",
            a:" directly on the Server Script",
            b:" directly into HTML pages",
            c:" All of the above",
            d:" None of the above",
            ans:"2"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q18:JavaScript code is written inside file having extension",
            a:" .js",
            b:" .jsc",
            c:" .j",
            d:" .javascript",
            ans:"1"
            },
            
            {
            question: "Q19:JavaScript is also called as",
            a:"Server Side Scripting Language",
            b:"Client Side Scripting Language",
            c:"All of the above",
            d:"None of the above",
            ans:"2"
            },
            {
            question: "Q20:JavaScript code can be called by using",
            a:"RMI",
            b:"Preprocessor",
            c:"Function / Method",
            d:"None of the above",
            ans:"3"
            }
        
        
];



